// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the following is correct about features of JavaScript?",
    answer: "All of the above.",
    options: [
      "JavaScript is a lightweight, interpreted programming language",
      "JavaScript is designed for creating network-centric applications",
      "JavaScript is complementary to and integrated with Java.",
      "All of the above."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following function of String object returns the characters in a string between two indexes into the string?",
    answer: "substring()",
    options: [
      "slice()",
      "split()",
      "substr()",
      "substring()"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following function of String object creates an HTML anchor that is used as a hypertext target?",
    answer: "anchor()",
    options: [
      "anchor()",
      "link()",
      "blink()",
      "big()"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following function of Array object represents the source code of an object?",
    answer: "toSource()",
    options: [
      "toSource()",
      "splice()",
      "toString()",
      "unshift()"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which built-in method returns the calling string value converted to lower case?",
    answer: "toLowerCase()",
    options: [
      "toLowerCase()",
      "toLower()",
      "changeCase(case)",
      "None of the above."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "_________ keyword is used to declare variables in javascript.",
    answer: "Var",
    options: [
      "Var",
      "Dim",
      "String",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which CSS property can provide to add an effect when changing from one style to another,without using Flash animations  or javascript?",
    answer: "Transitions",
    options: [
      "Associations",
      "Transitions",
      "Transistor",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "When a JavaScript object is sent to Java, the runtime engine creates a Java wrapper of type",
    answer: "JSObject",
    options: [
      "ScriptObject",
      "JSObject",
      "JavaObject",
      "Jobject"
   ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which of the following is not supported by older browsers?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "CSS",
      "Layers",
      "Frames",
      "All of the above"
   ]
},
{
   numb: 10,
   question: "What do you add to a template in order to control where page content goes?",
   answer: "Editable Regions",
   options: [
    "Text Frames",
    "HTML Controllers",
    "Editable Regions",
    "Page Content Controllers"
  ]
},
];